[narrator] After challenging Meruem
to a contest in order to buy time,
Pouf was outside the palace
scattering scales
[Shaiapouf] I must hurry, or Lord Meruem
will remember what he should not.
[man 1] We haven't moved forward at all.
What the hell is the matter?
What's going on up there?
[man 2] Shh! Keep quiet, all right?
[man 3] I heard all senior officers
have collapsed, one after another…
like puppets whose strings
have been cut.
[Shaiapouf] After giving the King
6/7 of my body,
I'm significantly weaker.
I've lost so much power.
The scales aren't scattering as well
as I would like.
And I don't see
any of Pitou's puppets around anywhere.
Does that mean the battle
with the boy is so intense,
that aura cannot be spared on puppets?
Even so, I need to hurry
and kill the woman
while there's still time.
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in English]
[singer singing in Japanese]
DEADLINE X TO X LIVE
Are you telling me that
they didn't run away?
Yeah.
And you better tie up their hands
and blindfold them.
I can't let them see me.
No time to explain.
I understand. That makes sense.
By the way, why did you bring him along?
[Welfin] Hmm? Huh?
that the woman's
in the underground warehouse.
Let them know that
we're looking to negotiate a deal.
Do that and you're free.
The fact that I'm doing
the enemy's bidding at all
may be enough to anger the King.
I'm not about to dig my own grave.
[Welfin] A lot better than you.
[Palm] It's absolutely critical
that he carries out his mission.
Welfin, once this is all over,
you're free.
[Welfin] Huh?
[Ikalgo] Then go find Gyro.
Huh?
What do you know?
Just who do you think you are, huh?
I know that,
[Welfin] How…
How did you know about…
my old name?
I never told anyone.
we were friends.
We were friends?
[Ikalgo] From before.
[Welfin] Yeah.
[Ikalgo] The Ants are our enemies.
Enemies of the NGL.
Take him with you.
[snarls]
how do you know?
Wait. What do you mean?
You just said you wanted me to find Gyro.
But I…
I don't know if he's alive.
I just know he has to be.
Huh?
[Ikalgo] We survived, didn't we?
So I know. He wouldn't let himself
get digested.
[snarls]
[engine starts]
[door buzzes]
[Welfin] Damn it.
Damn it!
[groans]
[Menthuthuyoupi] I really hope you're sure
about this, Pouf.
It's already been ten minutes,
and I don't see any sign
of Pitou returning.
[gasps]
[Welfin] Get out.
Untie yourselves and use
the truck to escape.
Once you're outside,
you'll realize what's going on.
[engine starts]
[beeps]
[door buzzes]
Stop!
-[tires screeching]
-Huh?
Wait. Sir Youpi?
[ominous music playing]
Sir Youpi.
Please, I need to get a message
to the King immediately.
Hmm?
[Menthuthuyoupi]
The underground warehouse?
[Welfin] Right.
They want to make a trade,
that woman for all their captured allies?
Is that what you're telling me?
That's right.
Go and tell the King at once.
He's gonna wanna know about it.
We're having a contest,
so I don't really need to tell the King.
If this is the kind of thing
Pouf was expecting,
well, he's even smarter than I thought.
[coughs]
All right. You can go.
Sir!
[Welfin] Chimera Ants are the enemy.
-Sir Youpi!
-Hmm?
[Welfin] I have a question for you, sir!
[Menthuthuyoupi] What is it?
Do you have any memories
from your former life?
Old memories, like before you changed.
Huh?
You're kidding. Of course not!
I'm Youpi, the Royal Guard!
And that's all I've ever been!
Don't ask me stupid questions!
What? I told you don't… Huh?
Hmm?
If you try to attack me, I'll fight back.
[grunts]
you stupid punk!
Yes.
even one single time.
[dramatic music playing]
-[high-pitched whine]
-[grunts]
[imperceptible]
[Shaiapouf sighs] That took much longer
than I expected.
Where's Youpi?
Youpi.
No. It can't be.
All right. We're okay now.
[Ikalgo] What do you mean?
Palm?
[Meruem] In that case,
I suppose it's all right for me to begin.
It's too dangerous!
-The game is--
-[Meruem] The game is off?
[gasps]
Then that means I have won.
You will tell me everything you know.
[whimpers]
As we know…
Pitou tried to save and protect her.
But Pouf, on the other hand,
tried to kill her.
To put it in another way,
she's a double-edged sword for the King.
Is it? All right.
But what about us?
How do you explain our situation?
Wouldn't you say that it's impossible
for Soldier Ants to side with humans?
They aren't mutually exclusive after all.
Both of these reactions make sense.
I guess. I'll concede that point for now.
But you said that we're okay,
so how do you know that?
[Palm] Twenty minutes have passed
since the initial wave of En
That's why I think we're okay.
Hmm.
Yeah, I still don't get it.
What the hell is going on here, Palm?
When En was first used,
I was carrying this girl on my back.
If the King had noticed that,
I'm sure he would have come
straight to me.
But he didn't,
because she was wrapped in my hair.
Hmm. I gotta admit, it sounds logical.
But I still don't quite see your point.
My point is that if she's covered,
Wait a minute. You're saying
let Knuckle and Meleoron die
To accomplish that,
Come on. Give me something.
The King will die soon.
He doesn't have very much time left.
[gasps]
In just a few hours,
There. That should do it.
[gasps]
No!
We are far worse!
[dramatic music playing]
[Shaiapouf] Pitou.
Pitou.
Where are you?
Pitou!
[groans]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time, "The Word Is You."
And it isn't Killua.
[Shaiapouf] Nothing less, nothing more.
[singer singing in Japanese]